<Root xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Key name="8" title="Angela's Incomplete Page">
How much time has passed since he returned back into the Light. The Reverbetation Ensemble, Roland, and following, the Head. Things too many to count transpired. And only now, with Angela's story at an end... I open this book, and dive into thought.

Though he ordered to keep this book hidden from all, strangely no one pays attention to it in the first place. Perhaps, better put at they're trying not to. Some Assistants asked what the book was in passing conversation, but they nod and go on their way from even with the simplest answers. Even the Library Director was no exception.
Perhaps they know the identity of this book in their unconscious. Telling themselves there's no good to be had in facing it once again and repressing their curiosity. And it is for that even the slightest bit of curiosity that makes it through the cracks is quickly subtracted by a passing response.

Indeed, that could be their response. But if that's truly what they respond with... I cannot but question what this child's hopes were for. Having heard her purpose in the Light and descended, but done nothing but tear open their wrath. I wonder what she felt, being sacrificed for the purposes of the Stage from beginning to end. If she had known one wipe with oblivion would've buried all, made everyone turn away, she may not have held that hope in the first place. For a mind selfish at it is, could we tryly say a revenge was in order.

Even with his personal request, sometimes the urge to reveal the true events of that day rears its head. But, every time, the face of that child appears in my mind. Her face, asking me if I hated her, was not a light one. It causes me to hesitate.
Even if their minds are naught but selfish, isn't it alright if that's all they're happy with. That may be what she was attempting to tell me. Or perhaps, even I am borrowing that child's view, attempting to justify myself. To face away from the truth of it all.

...Leaving the causation titled the City, we still yet live in a day repeating, leaving me wondering if our time as told by him would ever come. And if it was to, what form would it take. I can't hope to predict such. Yet, if I dare to hold a desire, it would be that it would be one to bring a tomorrow in which this poor child cough smile. Even if it's for that day only, for it to be one where sorrow could be erased and happiness with satisfaction could take its place.
  </Key>
  <Key name="11" title="An Arbiter's Page">
...
</Key>
  <Key name="12" title="A Recordkeeper's Page">
I cannot forget that instant, where I saw him who I believed I would never see again. In which he needed my strength, however feeble.

Though the Library now is Angela's E.G.O, the Library during that event was most llikely not strictly... hers. Light great enough to shine upon the entire city for 7 days would've been too tremendous to be beacon'd through a single vessel.
Why Carmen sent that child here, why he had his second coming... and the change that took place within me when he needed my strength would be impossible to explain excluding its specificity.

...though now, with the Library exiled in the Outskirts, his experiences and form is sometimes projected upon me during receptions. Angela passes over it as I having been affected when she was recreating Binah, but this...
Though I do not dare attempt to predict when the time he foretold would come, surely this happening is for that moment. And for that, I cannot provide a response to her speculations.
  </Key>
</Root>