<Root xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Key name="1" title="Paradise In Full Bloom">
If someone ordered you to redo something you've failed at, how would you feel? Some might resolve, "This time it will be different." But others might be unable to shake off the feeling of powerlessness they've already experienced, afraid to even think about it. And if, at the end of this feeling of powerlessness, you're overwhelmed by the guilt of having swallowed up others, even to the point of suicide, then that's even worse.

Even if she repeats it again, I don't know if she believes the outcome will be the same, or if she simply refuses to try again. But when she shapes me like this, I often collapse before I even take the first step. No matter how carefully I've crafted it, no matter how much strength I've poured into it, the moment her hand moves away from me, I'll melt and stain her feet.

After dozens of failures, she thought. If I'm so weak that I can't maintain my own form, wouldn't it be enough to put on a shell that can sustain me until I reach full maturity? By concealing the memories and forms of others, I can also mask the impact of my own fear of failure, killing two birds with one stone. As she struggled to decide whose image to imitate, she felt someone she hadn't seen by her side for a long time take a step forward.

As if listening to my greeting, she looked at me, melted into something, and asked what I was doing. Furious at her ignored greeting, she confidently announced her plan, its failures so far, and the remedies she had envisioned. Even though only one person was listening, she spoke confidently, using a variety of expressions and gestures as if she were standing before a crowd. It was as if she had revealed her ideals to everyone in her lifetime.

What did Ain feel after hearing all this? She waved a melted piece of me and angrily said, "Are my ideas so foolish?" Ignoring her reaction, I simply sighed. If he wasn't interested, he would have just watched me from the corner, as usual. The moment I tried to pull him away from me, he showed her a certain image.

"...Are you saying what I'm about to do now no different from what you did to Angela, Ain?"

Was it forcing someone who didn't want to move forward, claiming it was no different from what he'd done to Angela before? Or was it urging her to imitate the machine he'd built to fit the shell she desired? In the end, he didn't reveal his intentions, only muttering to himself, inaudible, as he returned to where he'd been. Unable to find a clear answer, she hesitated for a moment, but ultimately, she reshaped me.

Was it a shell that could withstand the turbulent waves, as she'd hoped, or a shell that suppressed the earnest cries of "not wanting to move forward" and forced action? I took the first step before her, and she breathed a sigh of relief, opening her eyes for the first time.

...

She had draped her own frail existence, ready to collapse if she couldn't even take a single step, over the memories of others, clinging to them. What was she hoping to achieve? I had some vague ideas in mind, but I didn't want to continue. I didn't know what had led to this tragedy.
</Key>
  <Key name="2" title="Angela">
Angelos. A messenger conveying God's will to the human world. Was the name Ain first created and intended for me simply a cog in his scheme? If so, then I, who passed it on to her, also wish for a cog in the wheel that replaced Ain and me. Ugliness is deeply rooted behind this beginning. Watching from afar as she struggled to comfort the assistant librarian, racked by fatigue and resentment, I suddenly remembered my first encounter with the designated librarians at Lobotomy Corporation.

But you looked at me with neither good nor ill will... Not to mention Hokma, who supported her according to Ain's orders. Those like Malkuth and Netzach, who viewed it positively and tried to atone for their actions and offer assistance, those like Chesed and Hod, who reduced the very meeting place they had tried to create to ash. Those who could not even smile and greeted them. Tipereth simply refused to face them. She simply stared at them without expressing any opinion, even dissenting from their designation.

If I force them to treat her, they won't refuse... Sitting here, I can finally understand why Ain is just watching. If the light that shines down alone determines everything between us, then we can't always rely on it to move forward. Even if someone is injured, collapsed on the ground, groaning, we can't always help on their behalf. Sometimes even this thought makes me feel sick to my stomach, thinking about quelling the first rebellion. I wonder if it's part of his vision for her. If this is the right direction I want, then regardless of whether it aligns with his, I have no choice but to follow my path.
</Key>
 <Key name="13" title="Red Mist">
I remember a quarrel among the assistant librarians on the art floor a few days before the Sixth Guild reception. "Why should I do this? I'm not interested in beer or anything like that. Just let me sleep." Regardless of his wishes, he was taken away by Angela at the next reception, resurrected from the dead.

They had no choice. No right to negotiate. Because we must spread the Light completely, and that resolve will not waver, we accepted Angela's deal. If Angela persists in her desire and attempts to use the Light, we will do everything in our power to stop her and ultimately perish. In the process, we will not care how many others die besides ourselves.

One day, when the moment of choice comes, will they turn a blind eye if the assistant librarians attempt to seize the Light in order to survive? They will also turn their knives on them without hesitation. Even Chesed and Hod, always so kind, hesitated. While it's possible to sympathize with the livestock being taken to the slaughterhouse and offer them kindness, it's impossible to release them when their owners are also being slaughtered.

If we fear even a single act of evil and dare not move forward, then nothing can be accomplished. We are prepared to die as the price. What else can we do? We can defend ourselves against our crimes when others in the world hold us accountable, but can we also say the same about the victims? Even in the city, where human life is considered worthless, aren't we trying to save those who are worth less than anything else?

The cost of this reserved choice was simply overlooked in the aftermath of the first rebellion, in the form of oblivion. Until now, without any dialogue, it has ultimately resulted in the extermination of one side. We gained everything we longed for, while they lost everything they longed for. It's a bitter, urban ending that we can never smile at.
</Key>
  <Key name="14" title="Assistant Librarian">
...
</Key>

</Root>