<BattleEffectTextRoot xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <effectTextList>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="keyword_lcangela_ch3_gebura_page">
		  <Name>Instinct</Name>
		  <Desc>This effect activates when this card deals 8 or more damage.</Desc>
	 </BattleEffectText>

    <!-- #region 침식 루트-->
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaDistortCarmenBufPhase1">
      <Name>Mark</Name>
      <Desc>Speed and power increase by {0}. Effects changes depending on whether the Librarian is present at the phase transition.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaDistortCarmenBufPhase2Ally">
      <Name>Brand</Name>
      <Desc>Dice power when targeting Blooming Paradise is reduced by {0}, and all characters with Brand take damage and stagger damage Blooming Paradise would have taken split evenly. At the end of the scene, if Blooming Paradise has no remaining dice, it is reduced by 1.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaDistortCarmenBufPhase2Enemy">
      <Name>Brand</Name>
      <Desc>Dice power increases by {0} and all characters with Brand take damage and stagger damage Blooming Paradise would have taken split evenly. At the end of the scene, if Blooming Paradise has no remaining dice, it is reduced by 1.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaDistortCarmenEnemyWhisper">
      <Name>Whisper</Name>
      <Desc>Each time this is gained, you receive 1-2 damage and Stagger damage. (For Apostles, this applies as Recovery.) When this value reaches 40, it disappears and you gain 1 Brand. if Blooming Paradise has no remaining dice at the end of the Scene, lose all Whispers.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <!-- #endregion -->


    <!-- #region 에고 루트 -->
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaInvitationEgoCollapse">
      <Name>E.G.O. Collapse</Name>
      <Desc>At the start of each stage of the Book Hunters' Stage, Angela takes {0}% of her maximum Stagger Resistance as Stagger damage. If this value reaches 100, you lose the encounter.
Decreases each time the Assistant Librarian's Panic is reset on Gebura's Stage.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaInvitationPanic1">
      <Name>Panic - Fortitude</Name>
      <Desc>Attacks allies other than Cocoon. Gain {0} Strength at the start of the Scene and increase damage dealt with attack dice by {1}%. </Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaInvitationPanic2">
      <Name>Panic - Prudence</Name>
      <Desc>Uses a card on a random character. Each time the dice is rolled, inflicts {0} Stagger damage to all characters. If Stagger Resistance is less than {1} at the end of the Scene, inflict {2} Stagger damage to all Assistant Librarians and then die.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaInvitationPanic3">
      <Name>Panic - Temperance</Name>
      <Desc>Uses a card on a random character. When using a card, inflicts {0} Stagger damage to the target. At the end of the scene, inflict Stagger damage to Angela equal to the number of dice remaining * {1}.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaInvitationPanic4">
      <Name>Panic - Justice</Name>
      <Desc>Attacks the Cocoon. When Clashing with a target that is not the Cocoon, the dice power increases by {0}.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaInvitationEgoLight">
      <Name>Blooming Light</Name>
      <Desc>If this becomes 0, you lose the reception, and if this is less than 5, you lose control of Speed Dice by the difference from 5 (so 3 would be 2 dice loss). At the start of the Scene, all allies recover {0}% of their health.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaInvitationEgoSin">
      <Name>Blooming Sin</Name>
      <Desc>When this character dies, the same amount of Blooming Sin is granted to Angela. If Angela has this effect, Blooming Light decreases by the value of this effect at the start of the Scene, and when clashing with ???' combat pages or when responding to ???'s Mass Attacks, your dice value becomes 0. (This effect triggers up to the Blooming Sin stacks per Scene.)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaInvitationEgoCorruption">
      <Name>E.G.O. Corruption</Name>
      <Desc>Don't be afraid. You'll be at ease soon.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <!-- #endregion -->


    <!-- #region 보상 -->
	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaOrdealRedCheer2">
		  <Name>March</Name>
		  <Desc>If the Emotion Coins are full when a card is used, immediately raise the Emotion level and grant March 2 to two random characters. (Priority given to non-march targets) Reduces by 1 at the end of each Scene.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="onlypage_lcangela_angela_stable">
			<Name>Angela Secretary's Exclusive</Name>
			<Desc>Can only be equipped on Angela (Secretary)'s core page.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="onlypage_lcangela_carmen_angela">
			<Name>Angela's Exclusive</Name>
			<Desc>Can only be equipped on Angela (Secretary)'s core page or Blooming Paradise's core page.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="onlypage_lcangela_carmen">
			<Name>Blooming Paradise's Exclusive</Name>
			<Desc>Can only be equipped on the core page in Blooming Paradise.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaCarmenSinBloom">
      <Name>Blooming Sin</Name>
      <Desc>X equals the sum of all the "Stagger Damage" effects activated by your Flow Control pages. If you are not Staggered at the end of an scene, your Qlipoth Counter increases by X.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaQlipothCounterCarmen">
      <Name>Qlipoth Counter</Name>
      <Desc>Reduced by card usage or passive abilities. If it is 1 or higher at the start of the scene, you become Staggered for the duration of that scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaCarmenBless">
      <Name>Mark</Name>
      <Desc>Gains additional effects based on the Flow Control settings of the Patron Librarian. Removed at the end of the scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaCarmenPaleHand">
      <Name>Pale Hands</Name>
      <Desc>Speed is reduced and damage and stagger damage taken from dice is increased (once per die). Removed at the end of the scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaCarmenObedience">
      <Name>Obedience</Name>
      <Desc>Uncontrollable. When acquiring an emotion coin (might just be positive?), share that emotion coin with the Patron Librarian and one other ally with this effect. This character will try to clash if able, but otherwise attacks the last target attacked by the Patron Librarian. If the Patron Librarian dies, you die.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaCarmenBless">
      <Name>Token</Name>
      <Desc/>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaCarmenAwe">
      <Name>Awe</Name>
      <Desc>Each time you win a clash or hit the Patron Librarian, decrease by 1. At the start of the Scene, reduce the Patron Librarian's Qliphoth counter by {0}, and you take {0}% of your maximum Stagger Resistance as Stagger damage.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangelaCarmenPaleHand">
      <Name>Pale Hands</Name>
      <Desc>Pale Hands has a stack equal to the amount of reduced speed in the scene, and damage and stagger damage taken from dice increases by {0}. This is removed at the end of the scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>


		<BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaQliphothSuppression_stable">
			<Name><![CDATA[Qliphoth Suppression : <color=#00ff00>Stable</color>]]></Name>
			<Desc>Maximum light increases by 1. When Staggered, all Qliphoth Counters are lost.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaQliphothSuppression_overclock">
			<Name><![CDATA[Qlipoth Suppression : <color=#ff0000>Overload</color>]]></Name>
			<Desc>At the start of the act, take Stagger damage equal to 2.5 times the number of Qliphoth Counters held.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaQliphothSuppression_ego">
			<Name>Qliphoth Suppression : Blooming</Name>
			<Desc>Maximum Light increases by 1, and applies the "Protection" effect to all allies at the start of the scene. Qliphoth Counters are reduced by the number of allies affected by the Protection effect.
If the Qliphoth Counter is 0 or higher when Staggered, it is reduced to 0 and this ability is lost. If the Qliphoth Counter is less than 0 when Staggered...</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaQliphothSuppression_distort">
			<Name><![CDATA[Qliphoth Suppression : <color=#ff0000>Distortion</color>]]></Name>
			<Desc>You can't Act. Unspecified. After an ally uses a card, each time a clash is lost or a tie occurs, the Qliphoth Counter increases by 1. For each ally's loses a clash or is hit, the Qliphoth Counter decreases by 1.
This effect is removed if your Qliphoth Counter is 1 or higher at the end of an scene. Otherwise, it increases by 1, and if another ally dies, it is fixed at 3.
At the end of the scene when this effect reaches 3...</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaAngelaBlessStack1">
      <Name>Purged 1 or more cards</Name>
      <Desc>Remove 2 status ailments from the target and reroll the speed die.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaAngelaBlessStack2">
      <Name>Purged 2 or more cards</Name>
      <Desc>Recovery and Strength bonuses are doubled.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaAngelaBlessStack3">
      <Name>Purged 3 or more cards</Name>
      <Desc>Recover 1 Light to yourself and the target.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaAngelaBinahSin1">
		  <Name>Big Eyes</Name>
		  <Desc>Gain 2 Counter Dice (Blunt, 4-8)</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaAngelaBinahSin2">
		  <Name>Small Beak</Name>
		  <Desc>Increase damage by the cost of the cards used in this scene.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaAngelaBinahSin3">
		  <Name>Long Arms</Name>
		  <Desc>At the end of an scene, apply status effects to all targets and yourself using the cards in the next scene.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>


		<BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaEgoBless">
			<Name>Blessing</Name>
			<Desc>Restore 1 Light and draw a Bookshelf. Reduce damage taken and Disorientation damage by 2, and increase damage dealt and Disorientation damage by 2. (Applies only once per die.) Disappears at the end of the act.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentQlipothOverloadAlly">
			<Name>Qlipoth Meltdown (Ally)</Name>
			<Desc>Angela triggers a success or failure response effect based on the number of times she uses the Bookshelf on the target she designates.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_qlipoth_meltdown_ally_1">
			<Name>Qlipoth Meltdown: Dawn (Ally)</Name>
			<Desc>When Angela uses a Bookshelf on a target (all targetable when using an area-of-effect Bookshelf), the value decreases by 1, and when she uses a Bookshelf on any other target, the value increases by 1.
If this effect is 0 at the end of the scene, Angela's Qlipoth counter increases by 2 and the cost of a random Bookshelf with a cost of 3 or more is reduced by 1.
			</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_qlipoth_meltdown_ally_2">
			<Name>Qlipoth Meltdown: Noon (Ally)</Name>
			<Desc>When Angela uses a Bookshelf on a target (all targets that can be designated when using an area-of-effect Bookshelf), the value decreases by 1, and when she uses a Bookshelf on any other target, the value increases by 1.
At the end of the scene, if this effect is 0, Angela's Qlipoth Counter is increased by 2, and the cost of a random Bookshelf with a cost of 3 or higher is reduced by 1. (Resets when used)
If this effect is 1 or higher, Angela's Qlipoth Counter is reduced by 5, and you gain 1 Strength.
			</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_qlipoth_meltdown_ally_3">
			<Name>Qlipoth Meltdown: Dusk (Ally)</Name>
			<Desc>When Angela uses a bookshelf on a target (all targets that can be designated when using an area-of-effect bookshelf), the value decreases by 1, and when she uses a bookshelf on any other target, the value increases by 1.
At the end of the scene, if this effect is 0, Angela's Qlipoth Counter increases by 2 and the cost of 2 random bookshelves with their original cost of 3 or more is reduced by 1. (Resets when used.)
If this effect is 1 or more, Angela's Qlipoth Counter decreases by 10 and she gains 2 Strength.
			</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_qlipoth_meltdown_midnight">
			<Name>Qlipoth Meltdown: Midnight (Ally)</Name>
			<Desc>When activated, marks are applied to two random bookshelves. If no invalid judgment (draw/joint loss) occurs when the target bookshelf is finished using, its value decreases by 1. (If the bookshelf is "Triggered When Equipped," the value decreases upon use.)
If this value is 0 at the end of the scene, Angela's Blooming Sin decreases by 1. If it is 1 or higher, Angela's Blooming Sin increases by 1.
If Angela is distracted or dies while under this effect, Angela's Blooming Sin is fixed at 3.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent4_Add2">
			<Name>When equipped with 2 or more copies</Name>
			<Desc>The number of targets increases by 1.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

		<BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent4_Add3">
			<Name>When equipped with 3 copies</Name>
			<Desc>he number of bookshelves that reduce the cost when a response is successful increases, and the number of Qliphoth counters that decrease when a response is unsuccessful increases.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>

    <!-- #endregion -->

    <!-- #region 컴포넌트 -->
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentCarmen">
      <Name>Distortion - Flow Control Card</Name>
      <Desc>If your Emotion Level is greater than or equal to the cost of the card, gain the corresponding effect. Does not activate if you are Staggered.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentQliphothParadox">
		  <Name>Paradox X</Name>
		  <Desc>If the Emotion Level at the end of the scene is higher than the cost of the corresponding card, the Qliphoth Counter increases by that amount.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal1_1">
		  <Name>Noon</Name>
		  <Desc>If all enemies are granted March, paralyze them.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal1_2">
		  <Name>Dusk</Name>
		  <Desc>If all enemies are granted March, empower allies.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal1_3">
		  <Name>Midnight</Name>
		  <Desc>If all enemies are granted March, gain Emotion Coins regardless of Emotion Level.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal2_1">
		  <Name>Noon</Name>
		  <Desc>The limit on the number of times a duplicate effect can be triggered is removed.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal2_2">
		  <Name>Dusk</Name>
		  <Desc>The "Total Clash Win" effect is triggered twice for speed dice with this effect applied.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal2_3">
		  <Name>Midnight</Name>
		  <Desc>The "On Use" effect for the Speed Dice with the effect applied is triggered twice.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal3_1">
		  <Name>Noon</Name>
		  <Desc>The "On Use" effect and the effect applied to the Dice among the nullified effects are triggered as your own effect.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal3_2">
		  <Name>Dusk</Name>
		  <Desc>The "On Combat Start" effect among the nullified effects is triggered as your own effect.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal3_3">
		  <Name>Midnight</Name>
		  <Desc>The effect applies to all speed dice slots, not just the first.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal4_1">
		  <Name>Noon</Name>
		  <Desc>Additional attacks are triggered even when using a card with a Qliphoth effect.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal4_2">
		  <Name>Dusk</Name>
		  <Desc>The original cost limit of a card is increased when using an additional attack.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

	  <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal4_3">
		  <Name>Midnight</Name>
		  <Desc>The additional attack activation limit is removed.</Desc>
	  </BattleEffectText>

    <!-- #endregion -->
  </effectTextList>
</BattleEffectTextRoot>