<BattleEffectTextRoot xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <effectTextList>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSceneBuf_bleeding">
      <Name>Bloody Tear</Name>
      <Desc>All characters do not lose Bleed stacks after rolling Offensive dice for this Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSceneBuf_fire">
      <Name>Burning Tear</Name>
      <Desc>Whenver a character takes Burn damage this Scene, all allies of that character take that damage too.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSceneBuf_power">
      <Name>Rotting Tear</Name>
      <Desc>All Power Increase effects are applied as Power Decrease effects for this Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSceneBuf_decay">
      <Name>Melting Tear</Name>
      <Desc>All Protection's damage reduction effect is applied as damage increase effect for this Scene.
When characters are hit, they take damage equal to Protection on them.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSceneBuf_asiyah">
      <Name>Qliphoth - Asiyah</Name>
      <Desc>Force clashes. Pages targeting this character cannot be removed from the Speed dice.
Pages targeted by this character have their target changed to a random Speed die of their target.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosPersistAsiyah">
      <Name>Qliphoth - Asiyah</Name>
      <Desc>Pages targeting this character cannot be removed from the Speed dice.
Pages targeted by this character have their target changed to a random Speed die of their target.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSceneBuf_briah">
      <Name>Qliphoth - Briah</Name>
      <Desc>Can clash only if the opponent's Speed is lower.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSceneBuf_atsilut">
      <Name>Qliphoth - Atziluth</Name>
      <Desc>Can clash only with the pages of the same Type (Melee/Ranged/Special).</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_malkuth">
      <Name>Malkuth</Name>
      <Desc>Whenever a librarian uses a page, increase the Cost of all copies of that page by 1 for the next Scene.

Destruction Condition: Dice in this Speed die lose 5 times in a clash against pages whose original Cost is 2 or lower (Progress: {0}/5)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
	<BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_yesod">
      <Name>Yesod</Name>
      <Desc>"Endured" resistances of all librarians are changed to "Weak".

Destruction Condition: Take 50 or more damage of the type this character is "Endured" to (Progress: {0}/50)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_hod">
      <Name>Hod</Name>
      <Desc>Whenever a character is inflicted with a status ailment, the amount inflicted is doubled.

Destruction Condition: This die is hit 5 times by a librarian with 5 or more positive statuses (Progress: {0}/5)

Librarian that is currently able to fulfill condition: {1}</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_netzach">
      <Name>Netzach</Name>
      <Desc>Recovery effects of all librarians are reduced by {0}%. (10% for every hit taken by this Speed die in the previous Scene)
If the reduction is higher than 100%, they take damage instead.

Destruction Condition: Take 50 or more damage in a single Scene</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_tiphereth">
      <Name>Tiphereth</Name>
      <Desc>At the start of the Scene, if librarian has used 4 or more unique pages in the previous Scene, they are inflicted with 5 Feeble, Disarm, and Erosion.

Destruction Condition: This die is hit by 5 or more unique pages (Progress: {0}/5)

Already hit by: {1}</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
	<BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_gebura">
      <Name>Gebura</Name>
      <Desc>Double the Power of the first die rolled by this character in a Scene. (Does not include responding to librarians' Mass Attacks)

Destruction Condition: Lose a clash against a die that has +10 or more Power</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_binah">
      <Name>Binah</Name>
      <Desc>Become unable to be inflicted with status ailments, and take half as much damage from non-attacks.

Destruction Condition: Lose 5 clashes against dice unaffected by Power gain or loss (Progress: {0}/5)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
	<BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_hokma">
      <Name>Hokma</Name>
      <Desc>Dice on the last page used by this character in a Scene gain '[On Hit] Deal damage equal to (Dice value)% of target's HP'

Destruction Condition: Take 150 or more damage from a single die targeting this Speed die (Including damage from the ability of that die)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
	<BattleEffectText ID="angelosSephiraDiceBuf_keter">
      <Name>Keter</Name>
      <Desc>This Speed die cannot be targetted.

If HP is higher than 1 at the start of the Scene, recover HP to 500.

Destruction Condition: Destroy all other Sephirah dice (Progress: {0}/9)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="angelos_shadow_power">
      <Name>Power Down</Name>
      <Desc>Dice Power -{0}</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
	
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSuppressBuf">
      <Name>Deterrence</Name>
      <Desc>Increases by 1 upon winning a clash.
Decreases by 1 upon losing a clash.
Increases by 20 on kill.
Decreases by 10 upon becoming Staggered.
If this character has the highest Deterrence among allies, all enemies will target this character at the start of the next Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="angelosSuppressBufPreview">
      <Name>Deterrence</Name>
      <Desc>Increases upon winning a clash or on kill, reduces upon losing a clash or becoming Staggered.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosAsiyah">
      <Name>Asiyah</Name>
      <Desc>Defensive dice on all pages in deck of this character are changed to Offensive.
On a successful hit, ignore target's resistances.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosYetsirah">
      <Name>Yetzirah</Name>
      <Desc>This effect affects all allies.
Boost the minimum roll value of all dice to the middle value of the original dice roll values.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosBeriah">
      <Name>Briah</Name>
      <Desc>This effect affects all allies.
On a successful hit, recover HP equal to 30% of damage dealt.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosResonance">
      <Name>Resonance</Name>
      <Desc>Activate addtional effects on combat start if there are other pages with [Resonance] effect being used.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosAsiyahPreview">
      <Name>Asiyah</Name>
      <Desc>Defensive dice on all pages in deck of this character are changed to Offensive.
On a successful hit, ignore target's resistances.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosYetsirahPreview">
      <Name>Yetzirah</Name>
      <Desc>This effect affects all allies.
Boost the minimum roll value of all dice to the middle value of the original dice roll values.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosBeriahPreview">
      <Name>Briah</Name>
      <Desc>This effect affects all allies.
On a successful hit, recover HP equal to 30% of damage dealt.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosGeburaOverload">
      <Name>Amplification</Name>
      <Desc>Deal and take {0}% more damage and become unaffected by Power Reduction effects.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaAngelosGeburaOverloadPreview">
      <Name>Amplification</Name>
      <Desc>Deal and take more damage and become unaffected by Power Reduction effects.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="LCAngelaBenjamin_clock">
      <Name>Fate</Name>
      <Desc>Increases by 1 at the start of each Scene and every time the sum of rolls of dice rolled by this character reaches 13.

Current sum: {0}</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="LCAngelaBenjamin_clock_reward">
      <Name>Fate</Name>
      <Desc>Increases by 1 at the start of each Scene and every time the sum of rolls of dice rolled by this character reaches 13.
Take {0}% more damage and Stagger damage. (Up to 50%, including damage from non-attacks)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="LCAngelaBenjamin_clock_reward_preview">
      <Name>Fate</Name>
      <Desc>Increases by 1 at the start of each Scene and every time the sum of rolls of dice rolled by this character reaches 13.
Take more damage and Stagger damage. (1% per 1 stack, Up to 50%, including damage from non-attacks)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaKeyword_gear1">
      <Name>Cannot Win Clashes</Name>
      <Desc>All Counter dice from this page always lose in a clash, but recycle regardless of the outcome of a clash.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaKeyword_gear2">
      <Name>Deflect Nullify</Name>
      <Desc>All Counter dice from this page, upon losing a clash, nullify incoming deflect damage.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="onlypage_lcangela_binah">
      <Name>Binah's Exclusive Page</Name>
      <Desc>Can only be set in the deck of An Arbiter's Key page.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="onlypage_lcangela_angela">
      <Name>Incomplete Angela's Exclusive Page</Name>
      <Desc>Can only be set in the deck of Angela's Incomplete Key page.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="onlypage_lcangela_hokma">
      <Name>Hokma's Exclusive Page</Name>
      <Desc>Can only be set in the deck of A Recordkeeper's Key page.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    
    <!-- REQUIRE RE_TRANSLATION -->

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaQlipothCounterAngela">
      <Name>Qliphoth Counter</Name>
      <Desc><![CDATA[Value can be less than 0. And depending on whether it exceeds 0, Qliphoth Deterrence will be either in either <color=#00ff00>Stable</color> or <color=#ff0000>Overload</color> state.]]></Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaQliphothSuppression_stable_ch2">
      <Name><![CDATA[Qliphoth Deterrence - <color=#00ff00>Stable</color>]]></Name>
      <Desc>Upon becoming Staggered, lose all stacks of Qliphoth Counter.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaQliphothSuppression_overclock_ch2">
      <Name><![CDATA[Qliphoth Deterrence - <color=#ff0000>Overload</color>]]></Name>
      <Desc>At the start of the Scene, take Stagger damage equal to 2.5x Qliphoth Counter.
If Staggered, do not recover from it until Qliphoth Counter becomes 1 or higher.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_qlipoth_meltdown_enemy_1_1">
      <Name>Qliphoth Meltdown - Dawn (Enemy)</Name>
      <Desc>Decreases by 1 upon losing a clash and when hit, increases by 1 upon winning a clash and on a successful hit.
If at 0 at the end of the Scene, Angela's Qliphoth Counter increases by 2, and this character gains 2 Fragile next Scene.
If at 1 or higher, Angela's Qliphoth Counter decreases by 3.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaOrdealRedCheer">
      <Name>Parade</Name>
      <Desc>Whenever Emotion Level rises, gain 2 Stagger Fragile next Scene. After using a Combat Page, if the character has enough Emotion Points to raise Emotion Level at the end of the Scene, do that immediately instead.
If the character wins the clash, loses the clash, or makes a successful hit 3 times in a row against the same target, inflict 2 Parade to target. (Resets when used against another target or different result occurs)
Lose 1 stack at the end of the Scene. When the amount of stacks reaches 0, purge this status.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <!-- The Beast -->
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaBinahKey1">
      <Name>Key</Name>
      <Desc>Ability of 'Small Beak' Combat Page changes to '[On Play,][Return to Hand] Take 5% of Max. HP as damage; lower the Cost of pages in hand whose Cost is 1 or higher by 1 until they're used'.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText> 

    <!-- Guardians of the Forest -->
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaBinahKey2">
      <Name>Key</Name>
      <Desc>If all five librarians have an Abnormality page, when using 'Twilight' E.G.O page, add a Blunt die (Roll: 1-4, Gain Power equal to Power Gain of all dice of all allies) to the dice queue.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText> 

    <!-- Peace -->
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaBinahKey3">
      <Name>Key</Name>
      <Desc>When inflicting Fairy to the character with 'Intruder', apply +1 additional stack.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText> 

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaHokmaSinBuf">
      <Name>Fanaticism</Name>
      <Desc>When a librarian uses 'Fanaticism' Combat Page, they take 8 damage and gain 1 Strength. If they do not have Abnormality pages, they additionally gain 1 Damage Up.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_ordeal_green_dicebuf_1">
      <Name></Name>
      <Desc>[On Hit] effects of the librarian's page targeting Speed die activate twice. (Once per librarian)
Lose this status at the end of the Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_ordeal_green_dicebuf_2">
      <Name></Name>
      <Desc>[On Hit] effects of the librarian's page targeting this Speed die activate twice.
Lose this status at the end of the Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_ordeal_green_dicebuf_3">
      <Name></Name>
      <Desc>[On Clash Win] and [On Hit] effects of the librarian's page targeting this Speed die activate twice.
Lose this status at the end of the Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcangela_ordeal_green_dicebuf_4">
      <Name></Name>
      <Desc>[On Use], [On Clash Win], and [On Hit] effects of the librarian's page targeting this Speed die activate twice.
Lose this status at the end of the Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="keywordLcAngelaQliphoth">
      <Name>Qliphoth X</Name>
      <Desc>When used, lower Qliphoth Counter by X.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>    

    <BattleEffectText ID="keyword_lcangela_ketersin_1">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - Changed by 0</Name>
      <Desc>Change the Cost of this page to a rnadom value between 0 and 3 until it's used.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="keyword_lcangela_ketersin_2">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - Changed by 1</Name>
      <Desc>Whenever user gains a positive status, recover 2 Stagger Resist.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="keyword_lcangela_ketersin_3">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - Changed by 2</Name>
      <Desc>Whenever user gains a positive status, give the same status effect to a random other ally as well, and they and user recover 2 Stagger Resist.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
    <BattleEffectText ID="keyword_lcangela_ketersin_4">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - Changed by 3 or More</Name>
      <Desc>Whenever user gains a positive status, give half of the same status effect (Rounded up) to all other allies, and all allies recover 2 HP and Stagger Resist.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="onlypage_lcangela_carmen_angela">
      <Name>Exclusive Page</Name>
      <Desc>Can only be set in the decks of Angela (Secretary) and Paradise in Full Bloom's Key pages.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>
	
	<BattleEffectText ID="buf_lcangela_dmg_down">
      <Name>All Damage Down</Name>
      <Desc>All Offensive dice the character plays deal {0} less damage and Stagger damage.
Can stack up to {1}.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>


    <!-- #region 앤젤라 멀티덱 컴포넌트 -->
    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent">
      <Name>Flow Control Page</Name>
      <Desc>By putting this page in the deck, corresponding effects will be obtained at the start of the reception.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentQlipothOverloadEnemy">
      <Name>Qliphoth Meltdown (Enemy)</Name>
      <Desc>For the Scene, response success and response failure effects activate depending on the number of times the character is hit.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentQlipothOverloadAlly">
      <Name>Qliphoth Meltdown (Ally)</Name>
      <Desc>For the Scene, response success and response failure effects activate depending on the number of times the character is hit.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent4_Add2">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 2 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Status is given to 1 more ally.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent4_Add3">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 3 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Status is given to 2 more allies, and the number of times required for response failure is increased.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent5_Add2">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 2 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Status is given to 2 more targets, and effect changes depending on whether or not response has occured.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent5_Add3">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 3 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Number of times required for response success is halved.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent6_Add2">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 2 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Increase Qliphoth Counter by this ability by 1 more.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent6_Add3">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 2 or More Copies in Deck and 3 or more Abnormality pages are selected</Name>
      <Desc>When using Instant page, restore 1 Light. (If target is an ally, they restore 1 Light too)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent6_Add4">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 3 or More Copies in Deck and 5 or more Abnormality pages are selected</Name>
      <Desc>Lower the Cost of all pages by 1.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent7_Add2">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 2 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Give 1 Endurance to all allies at the start of each Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponent7_Add3">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 3 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Give 1 Strength to all allies at the start of each Scene.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal">
      <Name>Ordeal Combat Page</Name>
      <Desc>Whenever Emotion Level rises, gain one of the Abnormality pages with the corresponding effect. Effect will be strengthened whenever the same page is gained. (Up to 2 times)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal_Add2">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 2 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Effect of this page is automatically strengthened whenever Emotion Level rises.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentOrdeal_Add3">
      <Name>Bonus Effect - 3 or More Copies in Deck</Name>
      <Desc>Increase the maximum amount of times the effect can be strengthened by 1.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentMidnight">
      <Name>Midnight E.G.O</Name>
      <Desc>At Emotion Level 4, obtain Combat Page with this effect. (Not treated as personal E.G.O page)</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentAngelosFix">
      <Name>Fixed Effect</Name>
      <Desc>If 'Memory of Torment' if in the deck, it will be converted to the corresponding version regardless of the current floor.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <BattleEffectText ID="lcAngelaMultiDeckComponentMyEgo">
      <Name>Unique E.G.O Page</Name>
      <Desc>At the start of the Act, this page will be moved to the alternative hand.</Desc>
    </BattleEffectText>

    <!-- #endregion -->

  </effectTextList>
</BattleEffectTextRoot>