<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">

	<!-- #region 3챕터 1무대 -->
	<PassiveDesc ID="30001">
		<Name>Sinking into Despair</Name>
		<Desc>Unable to act
Ends Stage 1 if your HP is 1.
If a "Book Hunter's Page" exists in the library and your HP is still below 1 after Scene 6...</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30002">
		<Name>Original Sin</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of each Scene, all characters gain 1 stack of "Damage Up" and you gain 1 stack of "Fragile".
Each trigger of this passive increases the number of stacks gained by 1.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30003">
		<Name>Broken Heart</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of each Scene, the Assistant Librarian with the fewest Abnormality Pages gains a special Abnormality Page and gains a +1 Speed ​​Dice for the duration of this Stage.
If Scene 6 occurs, all Assistant Librarians gain Abnormality Pages.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="30004">
		<Name>Dying Light</Name>
		<Desc>When the HP of any character other than yourself reaches 1 in this stage, restore their HP to full and reduce your HP by 50.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="30005">
		<Name>Betrayal</Name>
		<Desc>Target the librarian who attacked you with a page in the previous scene.
If no target is found, attack "Angela."</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="30006">
		<Name>Frenzy</Name>
		<Desc>If no damage is dealt in a scene, take 15% of your HP in damage and gain 1 stack of "Strength" and "Endurance" for the duration of this stage (this will not be triggered if you are Staggered at the start of the Scene).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="30007">
		<Name>Flesh-Eating Hatred</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of Scene 6, all passive abilities are removed and the Abnormality Page "Gaze" is gained.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30009">
		<Name>Understanding</Name>
		<Desc>Rolling an offensive dice against a Staggered target destroys that dice.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30010">
		<Name>Recorder</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of each Scene, remove one positive effect from a target with "Fate" that was Staggered in the previous Scene for every 2 stacks of "Fate" it possesses.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30011">
		<Name>The Eye Embracing the Past - Building the Future</Name>
		<Desc>Immune to Negative Status Effect Damage
Damage dealt by the player is not reduced by the value of the offensive dice.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30012">
		<Name>Faith</Name>
		<Desc>When rolling a "Defense" dice, if there is no clashing dice, place a random "Offense" dice with a maximum and minimum value equal to half of the dice (rounded up).
Dice rolled this way do not cause physical damage.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<!-- #endregion -->

	<!-- #region 침식루트 -->
	<PassiveDesc ID="30101">
		<Name>Pulsation</Name>
		<Desc>At the end of each Scene, if all surviving Assistant Librarians have "Mark," the book page will be changed.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30102">
		<Name>Whispering</Name>
		<Desc>When attacked, applies 1 "Mark" to the attacker. At the start of the 5th Scene, all characters will be marked 6 times.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30103">
		<Name>...</Name>
		<Desc>When switching phases, restores all librarians' health and Stagger Resist to full and changes the effect of "Mark."</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30104">
		<Name>Guidance</Name>
		<Desc>If you take fatal damage without a "Mark," you die. If you have a "Mark," you become unable to act for 1 Scene.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30105">
		<Name>Desire</Name>
		<Desc>Upon death, restore all other Assistant Librarians to full Hp and Stagger Resist, and increase all resistances by 1 level for the current phase.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30111">
		<Name>Serpent of Original Sin</Name>
		<Desc>Damage taken by you is shared among characters with a "Mark." Your dice are not destroyed by this effect.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30112">
		<Name>False Salvation</Name>
		<Desc>At the end of each Scene, if you have no remaining dice, remove all characters' Whisper and reduce their "Brand" by 1. If the character is a librarian, restore an additional 20 points of health and Stagger Resist.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30113">
		<Name>Whisper</Name>
		<Desc>When rolling the dice on the Scene, if neither the user nor the target includes you, apply 1 stack of Whisper to all characters except yourself.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30114">
		<Name>Slumber</Name>
		<Desc>At the end of using a card, if you do not lose clashes with the card, Stagger the target.
If the target is already Staggered, kill the target.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30115">
		<Name>Erosion of Light</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of each Scene, remove the page from your hand and place the page you intend to use in your hand. Page cost is 0.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30116">
		<Name>A Moment of Rest</Name>
		<Desc>If you take fatal damage while not possessing a "Brand," you lose all "Whispers" and enter a state of suspended animation.
Sudden animation ends at the end of the Scene you acquire a "Brand."</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30117">
		<Name>Follower</Name>
		<Desc>When you take fatal damage or become Staggered while possessing a "Brand," you consume 1 stack of "Brand" and restore all your health and Stagger Resist.
Each time this effect is triggered, you gain 1 stack of "Strength" and "Endurance" on this Scene (initialized when you suspend your own death).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30201">
		<Name>Actor on the Stage</Name>
		<Desc>Restarting the reception will start with the current stage.
All passive abilities will change when switching. (Select Cancel Reception on the Prepare Reception screen to reset the reception.)</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30202">
		<Name>Host of the Stage</Name>
		<Desc>When switching phases, at the start of this Scene, restore 2 points of Light to all allied characters and draw 1 page.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30203">
		<Name>Red Mist</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of each act, set your lowest Speed dice to infinity.
When rolling dice, increase the Power of all dice on the current page by +1 for every 2 points your Speed exceeds the target (up to +5).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30204">
		<Name> The Courage to Protect Others</Name>
		<Desc>On Combat Start, gain 2 Slash Counter dice (4-8).
If you have Counter dice, if "Hokma" is the target of a one-sided attack, redirect the attack to you. Your Counter dice are not consumed upon completion of use.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30206">
		<Name>Faith</Name>
		<Desc>When rolling a "Defense" die, if there is no clashing die, place a random "Offense" die with the maximum and minimum values equal to half of the die (rounded up).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!-- #endregion -->

	<!-- #region 에고 루트 -->
	<PassiveDesc ID="30301">
		<Name>Guilt</Name>
		<Desc>Gain 70 stacks of "Self-Collapse" upon starting the stage. Stagger damage from dice is converted to Stagger Resist.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30302">
		<Name>Self-destructive Impulse</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of the "Self-destructive Impulse" act, you inflict Stagger damage proportional to your "Self-Collapse" status.
If "Self-Collapse" reaches 100 or your character on stage becomes Staggered or dies, the reception fails.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30303">
		<Name>...</Name>
		<Desc>What hope is there in this hell...?</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30311">
		<Name>The Girl on the Other Side of the Stage</Name>
		<Desc>Each Scene, you switch control of your own stage with that of "Gebura" and "Hokma." When you restart the reception, you'll use the current stage.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30312">
		<Name>Hope</Name>
		<Desc>Winning a clash reduces your maximum HP by 8% and restores Angela's Stagger Resist.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30313">
		<Name>Continued Trust</Name>
		<Desc>Winning a clash 3/6 times in each Scene causes one Cocoon to use a special page instead of an area damage page in the next "Gubura" stage.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30321">
		<Name>Pulsation</Name>
		<Desc>Using a Ranged Page inflicts 20 Stagger Damage to all Assistant Librarians and causes them to Panic.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30322">
		<Name>Whispering</Name>
		<Desc>When struck, increases Angela's Self-Collapse by an amount equal to the die value, and causes all characters on stage to take Stagger Damage equal to twice the die value.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30323">
		<Name>Self-destructive Impulse</Name>
		<Desc>Summons two Assistant Librarians at the start of each act.
When an Assistant Librarian dies, increases Angela's Self-Collapse by 20.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>


	<PassiveDesc ID="30331">
		<Name>Broken Rationality</Name>
		<Desc>Stagger damage taken by the designated librarian is converted to Stagger Resist.
Die if you become Staggered.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30332">
		<Name>Sweeping Madness</Name>
		<Desc>Start the stage after gaining a random "Panic" status.
If Stagger Resist is fully restored, Angela's "Self-Collapse" stacks are reduced by 5 and her "Panic" progress is reset (limited to once per Scene).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30333">
		<Name>Gearwheel</Name>
		<Desc>At the end of each Scene, if Stagger Resist is at least 30%, your own Stagger Resist is reduced to 30%, Panic levels are increased by 2, and Angela's "Self-Collapse" stacks are increased.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30341">
		<Name>Actor on the Stage</Name>
		<Desc>E.G.O. manifests and all of your "Instinct" pages have a activation cost of 0.
Offensive dice deal no damage.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30342">
		<Name>Actor on Stage</Name>
		<Desc>When the Assistant Librarian initiates the "Panic" state due to its own attacks, it restores 50% Stagger Resist and restores the maximum number of Emotional Coins in one of its own E.G.O. pages.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30351">
		<Name>Host of the Stage</Name>
		<Desc>Restores all allied characters to full Light at the start of each "Gebura" stage.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30352">
		<Name>Recorder</Name>
		<Desc>When Rolling a defensive dice, gains +2 power. If the dice wins a clash, they can be used again (limited to one roll per dice).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30401">
		<Name>Prophet</Name>
		<Desc>When restarting a reception, the reception will begin with the current stage. If the "Blooming Light" is lost and the reception fails, the progress will be reset.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30402">
		<Name>Prologue</Name>
		<Desc>Gain 4 stacks of "Blooming Light" upon opening the stage.
If "Blooming Light" is less than 5, lose control of Speed dice inversely proportional to the number of stacks.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30403">
		<Name>Wish of Mutual Growth</Name>
		<Desc>Gain 1 stack of "Blooming Light" each time you grant "Book Hunter" a positive status.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30411">
		<Name>Book Hunter</Name>
		<Desc>Add 2 to the maximum and minimum dice rolls for "Knowledge" pages.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30412">
		<Name>Proof of Hope</Name>
		<Desc>If you or "Angela" is Staggered or dies, "Angela" loses all "Blooming Light."</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30421">
		<Name>Serpent of Original Sin</Name>
		<Desc>If there are other surviving allies, this character cannot be selected.
This effect changes at the end of the Scene when all other allies die.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30422">
		<Name>Postscript</Name>
		<Desc>If no clashes are lost in a Scene, apply 2 stacks of "Paralysis" to all librarians and cause Angela to lose 1 stack of "Blooming Light."
This effect changes at the end of the Scene when all other allies die.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30423">
		<Name>Blooming Paradise</Name>
		<Desc>Each time Angela fails to respond (hit/fail to roll) her own dice, she loses 1 stack of "Blooming Light" and is inflicted with 1 stack of "Paralysis" for the current and next acts.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30431">
		<Name>Scale of Sin</Name>
		<Desc>When the stage starts, you gain one of four "Trial" Abnormality pages and "Blooming Sin."</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="30432">
		<Name>Accept Everything</Name>
		<Desc>Upon death, your Abnormality pages and "Blooming Sin" will be transferred to "Angela."</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>




	<!-- #endregion -->

	
	<!-- #region 보상 -->
	<PassiveDesc ID="17">
		<Name>Legend of the Red Mist</Name>
		<Desc>+1 Speed Dice
Additional +1 after reaching Emotion Level 3 (unique passive)
Gain the E.G.O. Page "Blood Mist" upon starting a stage
If Emotion Level has reached Level 4 at the start of each Act, place "E.G.O. Manifestation" in your hand (can be triggered once per stage)</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="18">
		<Name>The Courage to Protect Others</Name>
		<Desc>Gain 2 Slash Counterattack Dice (4-8) when commanding a battle
If you have Counterattack Dice, if another friendly character is the target of a unilateral attack, redirect their attack to you for a counterattack. Your Counterattack Dice are not consumed upon use.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="20">
		<Name>Red Mist</Name>
		<Desc>All dice gain +2 power
Can use the E.G.O. page "Corpse"
Give 1 stack of "Blood Mist" when killing an enemy character
For each stack of "Blood Mist," all dice gain +1 power (up to +5)
If there are targetable enemies during an act and the player has not dealt at least 50 points of damage, at the end of the act, they will take 40% of their maximum Stagger Resist damage.
If they become confused, their "E.G.O. Manifestation" status will be removed.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="21">
		<Name>Blessing</Name>
		<Desc>The number of Abnormality pages you possess increases the minimum value of all dice by +1.
If all allied characters possess their own Abnormality pages, the maximum and minimum values of all dice will be increased by +1.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="51">
		<Name>Angela</Name>
		<Desc>When the stage starts, all friendly characters draw 2 pages.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="52">			
		<Name>Qliphoth Tree</Name>
		<Desc>When this character grants a positive status to another friendly character, the number of stacks gained increases by 1.
If this character grants a positive status to another friendly character using a battle page, this character gains an additional "Qliphoth" point.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="53">
		<Name>Pure Heart</Name>
		<Desc>Reduces the cost of all friendly characters' personal E.G.O. pages by 1 and reduces the required Emotion by half.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="54">
		<Name>Rising Star</Name>
		<Desc>When a full Emotion Coin is gained by a friendly character, it will be distributed to an unfilled friendly character.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="61">
		<Name>Serpent of Original Sin</Name>
		<Desc>When using a page, applies "Mark" to the target.
(Mark - increases or decreases the power of the designated target.)</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="62">
		<Name>Whispering</Name>
		<Desc>When an uncontrolled friendly character uses a page, the player's "Qliphoth" counter is reduced by 1.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="63">
		<Name>Slumber</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of each act, the player applies "Pale Hand" to a random enemy character (prioritizing the target last used by the player).
(Pale Hand - Speed -1-3, and damage and confusion damage received are proportional to the speed of the reduction.)</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>




	<PassiveDesc ID="1004">
		<Name>False Wish</Name>
		<Desc>(Only available for designated librarians)
When equipped with a Combat Page, you can equip a second deck that controls your passive ability.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="1005">
		<Name>Secretary</Name>
		<Desc>When equipped with a Combat Page, you can equip a second deck that controls your passive ability.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<PassiveDesc ID="1006">
		<Name>Gebura</Name>
		<Desc>
			Only available for the following characters:
-Language-level designated librarian
-General-level assistant librarian when Ain is a general-level designated librarian.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>


	<PassiveDesc ID="1007">
		<Name>Assistant Librarian</Name>
		<Desc>All passive abilities of this character will not trigger if no other designated librarians are alive.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<!-- 아군 사도 -->
	<PassiveDesc ID="661">
		<Name>Apostle</Name>
		<Desc>At the start of each act, remove the page in your hand and place the page you intend to use in your hand.
The cost of your own page is 0.
When assimilation is removed, restore 30% of your maximum HP and Stagger Resist.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>

	<!-- #endregion -->


</PassiveDescRoot>